<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.chromium.debug.feature"
      label="Remote Chromium JS Debugger"
      version="0.1.0"
      provider-name="The Chromium Authors"
      colocation-affinity="org.chromium.debug.feature">

   <description url="http://chromedevtools.googlecode.com/">
      A set of tools for developers using the Chromium browser
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.example.com/copyright">
      Copyright (c) 2009 The Chromium Authors. All rights reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://code.google.com/p/chromedevtools/wiki/License">
      Copyright (c) 2009 The Chromium Authors. All rights reserved.

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:
* Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
* Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer
in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
distribution.
* Neither the name of Google Inc. nor the names of its contributors
may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this
software without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS
&quot;AS IS&quot; AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT
NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT
SHALL THE COPYRIGHT OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT,
INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES
(INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS
OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION)
HOWEVER CAUSED
AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY,
OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY
OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY
OF SUCH DAMAGE.
   </license>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.ui" version="3.4.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui" version="3.4.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface.text" version="3.4.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.workbench.texteditor" version="3.4.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.editors" version="3.4.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.variables" version="3.2.100" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide" version="3.4.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="org.chromium.debug.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.1.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.chromium.debug.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.1.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
